{
    "subject": "resource/Cidade_Negra",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/linguistics/gold/hypernym",
    "object": "resource/Band",
    "human_readable": "Cidade Negra is a band.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9316983819007874,
            "question": "What type of group is Cidade Negra?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9061997532844543,
            "question": "Is Cidade Negra known for a specific genre of music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8635224103927612,
            "question": "Who are the members of Cidade Negra?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7886672019958496,
            "question": "What instruments are typically used by Cidade Negra?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7216581702232361,
            "question": "What is Cidade Negra known for musically?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7121680974960327,
            "question": "Where is Cidade Negra from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6974576711654663,
            "question": "When was Cidade Negra formed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6649755835533142,
            "question": "Has Cidade Negra released any albums?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5862677693367004,
            "question": "Are there any famous songs by Cidade Negra?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4203392565250397,
            "question": "Has Cidade Negra won any awards?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Cidade Negra is a band.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1135_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any famous songs by Cidade Negra?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1135_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has Cidade Negra released any albums?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1135_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When was Cidade Negra formed?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1135_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1135_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1135_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1135_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1135_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1135_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1135_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1135_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1135_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1135_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1135_99.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple that Cidade Negra is a band. The documents mention Cidade Negra as a Brazilian reggae band, with various details about their music and career. This suggests that they are indeed a musical group, or a \"band\", which aligns with the statement in the query."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents clearly state that Cidade Negra is a Brazilian reggae band, which supports the statement that Cidade Negra is a band."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}